{
    "id": "d8bdfa13630947598e8d95b16cf533df",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The principal called …………….. an explanation from the students.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "forth",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will happily carry ………………. your instructions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "off",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The stain wouldn’t come ……………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "in",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The actor carried ……………….. his role brilliantly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "out",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The manager called me …………….. and demanded an explanation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was called ……………….. to make a speech.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "upon"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "How did you come ……………….. that necklace?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "by",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Fear can bring …………….. a heart attack.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Somebody had broken ……………. through the back door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Four prisoners have broken ……………….. of the prison.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "away",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}